

# **MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI**

# **ABOUT ME**

I graduated from UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta majoring in Physics with a focus on Instrumentation Physics. Experience in analyzing experimental data has leverage my skills in identifying problems and troubleshooting capabilities. I have an understanding of hardware (computer and robot hardware) and software (Arduino, Python) based on my experience in disassembling and designing hardware and also creating program algorithms.

## CONTACT

Address : Jl. Kyai Maja RT 03/RW 03, Kel. Panunggangan,

Kec. Pinang, Kota Tangerang 15143

Phone Number : 081906795257

Email : mcgalihramdhan@gmail.com
Linkedin : linkedin.com/in/mcgalih/
Website : www.mcgalihramdhani.com

# **EDUCATION**

### Universitas Islam Negeri Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

May 2017 - January 2023

Bachelor of Science in Physics, GPA: 3.52/4.0

## COURSES

### RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Digital Marketing

#### RevoU (online course)

RevoU Fundamental Course Software Engineering

#### RevoU (online course)

RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics

# **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PPT)

Object oriented programming (Arduino, Python)
Web design (HTML, CSS, Javascript)

Graphic design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator)

# **EXPERIENCES**

#### **Laboratory Assistant** | 02/2021 - 12/2021

Pusat Laboratorium Terpadu UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

- Checking and calibrating the tools before doing experiments
- Leading and teaching the student how to operate and achieve the result as cited in the practitioner module for several courses
- Correcting and assessing student experimental reports

### **Graphic Designer** | 08/2018 - 01/2019

Ekspedisi 2018 event, HIMAFI UIN Syarif Hidayatullah Jakarta

- Create an instagram posts
- · Create a nametag design
- · Create a banner design

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Automatic moving Charity Box**

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Car

- Designed a storage box device that can move automatically and following the track line
- Control the device movement by placing a hand in front or behind of the device

#### **Card Security System Charity Box**

Github link: github.com/mcgalih/Charity-Box-Card

- Designed a storage box device that can only be opened by certain card(s)
- Can register a new card(s) as a key

Nomor liazah Nasional SK BAN-PT APT [Nilai]

452012023000168

: No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A] SK BAN-PT PRODI [Nilai] : No. 6929/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/S/XI/2020 [B]



# KEMENTERIAN AGAMA REPUBLIK INDONESIA UNIVERSITAS ISLAM NEGERI SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA



Memberikan Kepada:

# Mochamad Galih Ramdhani

Lahir pada tanggal 12 Januari 1999 di Tangerang

# IJAZAH SARJANA SAINS (S.Si.)

: Sains dan Teknologi **FAKULTAS** 

Fisika PROGRAM STUDI

NOMOR INDUK MAHASISWA : 11170970000002

NOMOR INDUK KEPENDUDUKAN / PASPOR : 3671111201990001

TANGGAL LULUS : 27 Januari 2023

Dengan segala hak dan kewajiban yang berhubungan dengan gelar akademik ini.





Jakarta, 24 Februari 2023

Dekan

Ir. Nashrul Haklem, S.Sl., M.T., Ph.D NIP.19710608 200501 1 0054



Universitas Islam Negeri SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH JAKARTA

#### TRANSKRIP AKADEMIK

Nomor Ijazah Nasional : 452012023300168

SK BAN-PT APT [N lai] : No. 25/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/II/2018 [A]

MOCHAMAD GALIH RAMDHANI

: Tangerang, 12 Januari 1999

: 11170970000002

: 31

Judul Skripsi

Rancang Bangun Kotak Amal Berjalan Otomatis Dengan Fungsi Deteksi Gelap-Terang Lantai.

Nomor Transkrip : B.F.9.ER 073692.2023

: Sains dan Teknologi Fakultas

Program Studi

Tempat/Tgl.Lahir

: Fisika

IPK

NIM

Jenjang

Jumlah Kredit

3,52

: 161 SKS

Tanggal Lulus	:	27 Januari 2023	Predikat Kelulusan	2	Sangat Memuaskan		

Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS	Nilai	Kode Matakuliah	SKS Nilai	Kode	Matakuliah	SKS Nila
HS 6003	BAHASA ARAB	3	A	FIE 4078	PEMROGRAMAN SISTEM INSTRUMENTASI	3	Α					
HS 6001	BAHASA INDONESIA	3	A	ris 5082	PENDAHULJAN FISIKA INTI	4	Α					
HS 6002	BAHASA INGGRIS	3	В	POL 2002	PENDIDIKAN KEWARGANEGARAAN	2	5					
10 2019	BICLOGI JMUN	2	В	FIS 5072	PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	2	4					
TS 6069	DASAR-DASAR TELEKOMUNIKASI	3	A	FIS 4010	PRAKTEK BENGKEL	2	4					
IS 4017	EKSPERIMEN FISIKA 1	2	В	ABI 6027	PRAKTEK KERLA LAPANGAN	3	Д					
IS 6017	EKSPERIMEN FISIKA 2	2	В	FIS 4031	PRAKTIKUM ELEKTRONIKA	1	В					
IS 5142	ELEKTORNIKA LANJUT	2	В	FIS 6139	PRAKTIKUM ELEKTRONIKA LANJUT	1	A	Marie Control of the				
18 4033	ELEKTRONIKA	3	В	FIS 3013	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 1	1	Α	The state of the s				
IS 3003	FISIKA DASAR I	3	Α	FI3 4014	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA DASAR 2	1	٨			ľ		
18 4003	FISIKA DASAR 2	3	в	FIS 4092	PRAKTIKUM FISIKA KOMPUTASI	1	В					
IS 4015	FISIKA KOMPUTAS	3	В	SAR 2002	PRAKTIKUM IBADAH	1	A					
IS 6004	FISIKA KUANTUM	4	Α	KIM 3047	PRAKTIKUM KIMIA DASAK	1	C					
13 5005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA 2	4	В	FIS 6029	PRAKT KUM MICROPROSESOR	1	Α	A STATE OF THE PERSON NAMED IN COLUMN TWO IS NOT THE OWNER.				
IS 4005	FISIKA MATEMATIKA I	4	В	FIS 5081	PRAKT KUM PENGOLAHAN SINYAL DIGITAL	1	A	A STATE OF THE STA				
IS 5007	FISIKA MODERN	3	А	SAR 2001	PRAKTIK JM QIROAH	1	В	100000000000000000000000000000000000000				
15 6018	FISIKA STATISTIK	1	В	FIS 3089	PRAKTIKUM SISTEM DIGI <mark>TA</mark> L	1	Α					
1S 502C	FISIKA ZAT PADAT	4	Α	TIS 3088	PRAKTIKUM SISTEM KENDALI	1	A					
FT 2237	GELOMBANG	3	В	FIS 5074	FOBOTIK	3	Α					
15 4002	ILMU PEDAGOGIK	2	В	JIN 4265	SEMINAR SKRIPSI	1	Α					
IS 5071	INSTRUMENTASI FISIKA MEDIS	3	В	F185070	SISTEM DIGITAL	2	A					
A G 2002	ISLAM DAN ILMU PENGETAHUAN	3	Α	FIS 6074	SISTEM KENDAL	2	Α	Market Market				
MAT 3018	KA_KU_US 1	.9.	A	FIS 8065	SISTEM SENSOR	3	В			West .		
1AT 4018	KALKULUS 2	3	В	STA3023	STATISTIKA	3	В	and the second s			D	
ABI 2019	KEW RAUSA IAAN	2	В	SAG 6001	MAJSHIGHTS	4	А			Jakar.a, 24 Feb	uari 2023	
CIM 3015	EIMIA DASAR	2	B	FIE 6072	TEORI RANGKAIAN	5	А		1	Dekan	0	
ABI 5013	KULIAH KERJA NYATA (KKN)	3	Α	FIS 5014	THERMODINAMIKA	5	Α		1/4	COX. X	•	
IS 3083	MEDAN ELEKTROMAGNET 1	4	ь	ABI 9014	SKRIPSI	6	A		1/2/			
TIS 7085	MEDAN ELKTROMAGNET 2	3	В						( *	· UI	ern, S.Si., M.T., Ph.D	
IS 5021	MEKANIKA	4	В							NIP 19:10608		
IS 6021	MEKANIKA KI ASIKA	Ž.	A						1/18	4KAR 19 10608	0000110051	
MA" 4036	METODE NUMERIK	2	Α							BY IK INDO		
ABI 3021	METODOLOGI PENELITIAN FISIKA	3	A							III THE LITTLE OF		
FIS 506?	MICROPROSESOR	3	С					EN STATE OF THE ST				
POL 2001	PANCASILA	2	Λ	1						and the same of th		